Stjepan Grgić

Digital Product Designer

grgic.stjepan@gmail.com | +44 7732 877 679 | London stjepangrgic.com | linkedin.com/in/stjepangrgic

Summary —

Analytical and creative designer with over six years of experience in both startups and advertising agencies looking to join a challenging position with the ability to have ownership, responsibility and grow as a professional and as a person.

Work Experience -

Sabbatical / Travel break | January 2019 - September 2019

OptimoRoute | optimoroute.com

Lead UI/UX Designer | July 2017 - January 2019 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Worked on improving the experience of existing tools to enable businesses to run planning and delivery optimisations more efficiently.
- Involved in creating and designing the user experience and interface of new product features (Real-time Order Tracking, Customer notifications, Delivery breadcrumbs) from the ground up.
- Lead design projects (landing pages, marketing campaigns, presentations, sales collateral) for the OptimoRoute marketing and sales team

Axilis | axilis.com

Lead UI/UX Designer | March 2017 - July 2017 | Zagreb, Croatia

• Lead design of a healthcare SaaS product for the US based client. That included design and experience of Android based tablet and phone applications as well as an admin web application.

Underlayer

Founder & Digital Product Designer | December 2015 - July 2017 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Personal design studio.
- Lead user experience and user interfaces design for multiple projects, some of which are:
 - Agrivi | stjepangrgic.com/work/agrivi (case study)
 - Memgraph | memgraph.com
 - HCV Dnevnik (iOS App) | App store link
 - TalkBook | talkbook.co

Vibby | <u>vibby.com</u> | <u>stjepangrgic.com/work/vibby</u> (case study) **Product Designer** | March 2015 – January 2016 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Responsible for designing user experience and interface of every aspect of the product video player, 'vib' creation process, profiles, dashboard, explore page...
- Created countless wireframes and interactive prototypes.
- Involved in frontend development and 'sliced' online player, as well as the majority of other features of the web application.
- Designed new branding, presentations for investors, business cards, shirts ...

Skills

User Experience Design

Visual Design

Interactive Design

Sketching

Wireframing

Prototyping

Mockups

Design System

Problem Solving

Product Strategy

Product Vision

HTML and CSS

JavaScript Git

After Effects Animation

Drawing

Photography

Tools

Sketch

Figma

InVision App

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe After Effects

Principle

Google Analytics

Personal Skills

- Critical thinker
- Problem solver
- Great Listener
- Open-Minded
- Ability to adapt to multicultural environments
- Attention to details

Languages

- Croatian Native proficiency
- English Professional working proficiency
- German Elementary proficiency

Hobbies / In free time

- Reading as much as possible
- Photography
- Drawing and Painting

Grey Zagreb | grey.com/croatia

Digital Designer | July 2014 - March 2015 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Worked on a wide range of advertising campaigns for clients like A1 Telekom Austria Group, Microsoft Mobile, Erste Bank Croatia and Croatian National Tourist Board
- Featured projects:
 - Share Istria | Istrian Tourist Board | stjepangrgic.com/work/share-istria (case study)
 - Vip Xmas Chat | A1 Telekom | stjepangrgic.com/work/vip-xmass-chat (case study)

$\textbf{Virtus dizajn} \mid \underline{\text{virtus-dizajn.com}}$

Junior Web Designer & Developer | September 2013 - April 2014 | Zagreb, Croatia

- Designed websites for various local small business.
- Converted designs to HTML and CSS pages.
 - www.alati.info
 - www.liderizalidere.eu/hr/
 - www.bazeni-jerkic.com
 - www.klimaexpert.hr

Točka | tocka.co

Junior designer | July 2013 - September 2013 | Požega, Croatia

- Assisted the team in various design projects.
- Designed a technical manual book for C-DESIGN Fashion software for a local textile design school.

□ -1 + :		
Education		
Luucation		

University of Zagreb, Faculty of Graphic Arts

Bachelor of Arts - BA (Dropout) | grf.unizg.hr/en/ | 2010 - 2013 | Zagreb, Croatia

Other training / online courses	
---------------------------------	--

Coursera

- Gamification, University of Pennsylvania
- Introduction to Psychology, University of Toronto
- Interaction Design Specialization, University of California San Diego

Other

I have gone through many courses from Lynda.com, SkillShare, TutsPlus, DigitalTutors ...